<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<gameList>
  <game>
    <path>./SPEAR.EXE</path>
    <name>Spear of Destiny</name>
    <desc>It's World War II and you are B.J. Blazkowicz, the Allies' most valuable agent. In the midst of the German Blitzkrieg, the Spear that pierced the side of Christ is taken from Versailles by the Nazis and secured in the impregnable Castle Wolfenstein. According to legend, no man can be defeated when he has the Spear. Hitler believes himself to be invincible with the power of the Spear as his brutal army sweeps across Europe.Your mission is to infiltrate the heavily guarded Nazi stronghold and recapture the Spear from an already unbalanced Hitler. The loss of his most coveted weapon could push him over the edge. It could also get you ripped to pieces.Spear of Destiny is a prequel to Wolfenstein 3-D. It is a first-person shooter that uses the same engine and has the same gameplay, however the game is not divided into 6 separate episodes - all the levels are one long episode. The enemies and weapons are pretty much the same as in Wolfenstein 3-D. Only new additions include: new bosses, a new type of enemy, and a new pickup (a large box of ammo). 
</desc>
    <releasedate>19920918T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>id Software</developer>
    <publisher>FormGen, Inc.</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter-Shooter / 1st person</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./images/Spear of Destiny.png</image>
    <genreid>259</genreid>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./WOLF3D.EXE</path>
    <name>Wolfenstein 3D</name>
    <desc>The first three episodes of the game focus on William "B.J." Blazkowicz's attempts to escape from Castle Wolfenstein and overthrow the Nazi regime.

In the first episode, Escape from Castle Wolfenstein, B.J., an Allied spy, has been captured while trying to find the plans for Operation Eisenfaust, and was imprisoned in Castle Wolfenstein. Initially armed only with a knife and a Walther P38 (obtained by overpowering the guard in his cell), B.J. tries to escape the castle prison. Taking on SS guards, he eventually finds himself face to face with head prison guard Hans Grosse.

In the second episode, Operation: Eisenfaust, B.J. finds out that the operation is real, and that Nazis are creating an army of undead mutants in Castle Hollehammer. B.J. enters the castle and confronts the mad scientist Dr. Schabbs, creator of the mutants. His defeat signals the end of this biological war.

Die, Führer, Die! is, chronologically, the final episode. Fighting through Nazi soldiers, and attacking the bunker under the Reichstag, he finds himself up against Adolf Hitler himself (equipped with a robotic suit and 4 Gatling guns).</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>id Software</developer>
    <publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter-Shooter / 1st person</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./images/Wolfenstein 3D.png</image>
    <video>./videos/Wolfenstein 3D.mp4</video>
    <genreid>259</genreid>
  </game>
</gameList>